[{"answer": "Well, sometimes if I have enough energy to.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "And have you seen (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, I don't want to speak for the president about Rick Santorum's comment.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Does he feel that the emotions can all be kept in check?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Credibility issue -- no.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Finally, as we look at the forthcoming election and the battle hotting up, what do you identify now, given you're so closely involved with this campaign -- is there a slight credibility issue with his dramatic U-turn on the super PACs?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Exactly what I said.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "ORGAN: And let me just say that when the president is on the record of saying that these PACs are a threat to democracy, how can he have the brass neck to now support them?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Is that how we are leaving things?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "No you were christened James Todd Smith.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "That ruins it a little bit, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I think Todd works just fine.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "What is -- what is a respectful way?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "I feel great.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "How are you feeling about the Grammy's?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Without a doubt.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Let's be honest -- winnings better than losing, right?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well let -- let me ask you a difficult question.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "And I think just on a worldwide level, no democracy, you know, no democratic, you know, government is like just doling out all of the state secrets and all of the various nuances and dynamics that effect the decision making that goes on in the inner sanctum, you know?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Of course it is.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Is America still the country of that opportunity do you think?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "What do -- by my mantra recently on the show --", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "I'm an Independent, you know?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I think in order to keep America great, we have to keep America creative.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "How do we keep America great?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Look at me.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "And when you talk to people in that position, what do you say to them to inspire them?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, there was this woman, her name was Ellen Griffith, and that was my grandmother and, you know, may she rest in peace.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "When you look back, what was it about you that allowed you to get out of that trap?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "You have to look at all the people in the world that are successful and you have synthesize all of those positions, those people, those goals they achieved, the things they did, the heroic moments.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What do you do if you have no one?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Before I got stuck with you, Sam Handle (ph) was an international brand.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "You know someone in Belgium?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Five years to the day.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Yes, right, kind of like guys who have one letter of the alphabet for a first name?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "That's harsh.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "What would you do?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "You know, I've got to tell you, you know, I grew up --", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Chris Brown, Cold Play, Rihanna, Bruce Springsteen -- who do you get excited by?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Eat your soup, let her talk.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What have you learned about yourself through that process?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Did you pick up on Jennifer then?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "And you are living, walking proof that these shows, which often get derided by critics, really can actually produce world class stars, can't they?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "You know, I had that little moment right there, very briefly.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "What were you thinking?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What was the moment for you when you realized that you were going to make it?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Now that I didn't know.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Could you feel it?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Ooh, goodness.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What was the moment when you knew it was going to be a smash and you and your career were never going to look back?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Sometimes if I have enough energy to.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Do you sing like that in the bath?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "She really ranks right up there.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Where does this lady rank?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "You know -- well, I try not to pay much attention to it, because you will go bonkers.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What is like being Jennifer Hudson, with all of this nonsense being written about you?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "First of all, I have to give credit to God and also my upbringing.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Because that's what has always impressed me about you, is this inner strength that you have?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Definitely, definitely, every day.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Impending marriage?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Oh my goodness, again, my faith in God, you know, family.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "What are the core values you think you got from your mother and your grandmother that you can take forward?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "Does he know this?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "It started the year I started Arista Records.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "What is the thinking behind it?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I will tell you the show will open with Tony Bennett.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Tantalize me?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "You know, I would say.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Greatest living crooner?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "First of all, it would be very painful, to listen to one song.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Here is a question for you, and I have always wondered what your answer would be, if I could only allow you to listen to one song for the rest of your life, on repeat, what would it be?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I think it's going to have to be, A, an improved campaign.", "docId": "120212pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "When you look at what's happening with America now, what do you think the answer is to get America fired up again?", "qSentId": 617}]